# **Shakhor Smith**

WordPress & Front-End Web Developer with 1 year of experience. I'm a self-taught developer who taught myself server-side scripting language (PHP), structured query language (SQL) and front-end frameworks (JavaScript, jQuery) with the goal to continue growing to become a Full Stack Developer.

4288 Leola Rd
Douglasville, GA 30135
(678) 333-1889
shakhorsmith@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/shakhor-smith
github.com/smithmanny
shakhorsmith.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Web Developer/The Flag Company - Acworth, GA

2017 - PRESENT

- Work closely with developer and designers to build mobile responsive websites
- Find and fix bugs to ensure best customer experience
- Work on back-end projects using PHP and MySQL

#### Freelancer/Austell, GA

2017 - PRESENT

• Design and build websites based on client needs

#### Order Selector/Publix Warehouse - Austell, GA

2015 - 2016

- Build custom orders for retail stores and maintain accuracy of order
- Constantly surpassed daily production goal by 20%

#### **EDUCATION**

Computer Science/Georgia State University – B.S.

2016 - Present

#### **LANGUAGES**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- PHP
- MySQL
- Node/Express

# Frameworks

- Bootstrap
- Sass
- Jquery
- Symfony
- Twig
- React

#### Extras

- Git
- Gulp
- NPM
- WordPress